Logan Reynolds

Hi, my name is Logan.

I'm passionate about providing quality Web Design, Software Engineering, UI/UX Design service in the San Francisco area. I always go above and beyond to ensure I get the job done right the first time. My work stands out because I pay close attention to all the details of the job. I've been doing Web Design, Software Engineering, UI/UX Design work for 10+ years now, and I love it because it gives me the chance to have fun with computer programming by designing applications that everybody loves. I look forward to working with you to help meet all your Web Design, Software Engineering, UI/UX Design needs.

EXPERIENCE

Meda — Software Engineering Internship (Full Stack) — 2020 - PRESENT

 Worked on front end & back end project using HTML5, CSS3, GitHub, JavaScript, Angular, Bootstrap, MongoDB, Node.js, Expres.js and more.

Craigslist & More — Freelancing in Web Development — 2019 - PRESENT

 Worked on the development of application, websites & more for clients seeking a Web Design, Software Engineering or UI/UX Design contractor.

Amazon.com — Independent Content Creator — 2018 - PRESENT

- Orchestrated the publication of 12 ebooks on Amazon including paper & Audible publication of books.
- Gave ideas & directed ghostwriters in realizing those ides as published works. Designed eight covers.
- Improved overall look & feel for the works in question using my programming skills.

McDonald's, San Francisco — Manager — 2015 - 2018

- Supervised over 10 employees per shift, maintaining over a dozen schedules.
- Ordered 90% of the products, scheduled delivery, repaired office equipment, and handled conflict resolution.
- Coordinated the on-boarding of Uber Eats technology & processes in store driving up sales at least twofold
- Ran store on my own entirely on my own for multiple hours while continuing to contact employees.

EDUCATION & VOLUNTEERING

Make School, San Francisco — CS Bachelor's Degree — 2022

- Bachelor's degree in applied computer science.
- Concentrations include but are not limited to mobile development, web development (full stack) & data science/machine learning.
- Languages & frameworks include but are not limited to Python, JavaScript, Swift, Go, Flask, Django, Node.js, React.js, UIKit, CoreData, Foundation, NumPy, Pandas, Scikit-Learn, Keras & TensorFlow.

Code Tenderloin, San Francisco — Coding Bootcamp — 2019

 Participated in an intensive 6-week program to develop skills in HTML, CSS, Javascript & completed over 90 assignments to hone full stack web development skills.

Noisebridge, San Francisco — Programming Classes — 2019

• Studied Python2 & Python3 at Noisebridge. I am currently studying C# & Unity.

Code The Dream, www.codethedream.org — Coding Bootcamp — 2019

• Completing an online course in Ruby on Rails & AWS with Code The Dream.

Online Learning — Software Engineering | UI/UX Design Classes — 2014

 Study on Linda also known as "LinkedIn Learning", Hacker Rank, CodePen.io, Team Treehouse, Code Cademy, GitHub Learning Lab, Khan Academy, Udacity & so much more.

DVC, PleasantHill, CA — College — 2014

Classes in Business, Art Drawing, UI/UX Design, HTML, Dreamweaver, & Photoshop (intro & advanced)

Rainbow Community Center, Concord, CA — Volunteer Work — 2011 - 2014

• Advocacy for LBTQ+ community, front desk operations & web development.

SRVHS & Vanguard School, CA & FL — High School Diploma — 2010

• Classes in improving typing speed, HTML, images & video editing.

Software Engineer

10+ yrs experience in tech starting in High

San Francisco, CA

(415) 886-0145

EngineerLWR@gmail.com

SKILLS

- Programmer Experience in: HTML5, CSS3, Javascript ES6, Node.js, DOM, Bootstrap, NPM, Python3, Ruby, Rails, C#, Unity, Express.js, React.js, Pug, Command Line, Git & GiHub, Phaser, Game Dev, WordPress, CI/CD, Sass, AWS & Adobe Creative Suite.
- 10+ yrs expertise in creative tools to include entire Adobe suite (e.g., Photoshop) & Sketch.
- Retail and marketing professional -Manager of McDonalds for three years.

SAMPLE CREATIVE WORK

eBook covers, ArtDM — 2018

- "Make Money with Kindle eBooks" www.amazon.com/dp/B07JMH15ZY
- ➤ "Make Money through Real Estate Investing"
- www.amazon.com/dp/B07JLDY72B
- ➤ "Get a (Real Estate) Life!"
 www.amazon.com/dp/B07JGCRTDP
- ➤ "Make Money with YouTube"
 www.amazon.com/dp/B07JL5X1TV

Websites, apps, games & more,

Software Engineering — 2019

- ➤ "Dish Submitter Website"
 | wrgithub.github.io/dish-advanced/main
- ➤"Pong like game"
- lwrgithub.github.io/game1
- ➤"Phaser JS ES6 Game"
- lwrgithub.github.io/phaser-game/index
- ➤"Interactive Animation"
- lwrgithub.github.io/css-js-project/Interact iveAnimation
- ➤"Four In A Row"
- lwrgithub.github.io/fourInARow/index

PROGRAMMING PORTFOLIO

Software Engineer Portfolio Website

➤LWRGitHub.GitHub.io

GitHub

> github.com/LWRGitHub